export const JSQuestions = [
    // Question 1
    {
        question: "Which of the following statements about Javascript is true?",
        optionA: "Javascript is a dynamically typed language",
        optionB: "Javascript is a statically typed language",
        optionC: "Javascript is a general-purpose programming language",
        optionD: "Both A and C",
        answer: "optionD",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
    // Question 2
    {
        question: "True of false: Javascript is a multi-threaded language.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: false,
    },
    // Question 3
    {
        question: "Which operator is used to express whether two compared values are NOT equal?",
        optionA: "<>",
        optionB: "!==",
        optionC: "==!",
        optionD: "~",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
    // Question 4
    {
        question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable that cannot be reassigned?",
        optionA: "var",
        optionB: "let",
        optionC: "this",
        optionD: "const",
        answer: "optionD",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
    // Question 5
    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a supported data type in Javascript?",
        optionA: "Boolean",
        optionB: "Number",
        optionC: "Algoritm",
        optionD: "Object",
        answer: "optionC",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
    // Question 6
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used to write a single-line comment in Javascript?",
        optionA: "$$",
        optionB: "//",
        optionC: "+-+",
        optionD: "<>",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
    // Question 7
    {
        question: "Which keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function?",
        optionA: "async",
        optionB: "null",
        optionC: "await",
        optionD: "asyncFunc",
        answer: "optionA",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
    // Question 8
    {
        question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        optionA: "Date()",
        optionB: "toString()",
        optionC: "forEach()",
        optionD: "stringify()",
        answer: "optionD",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
    // Question 9
    {
        question: "Which of the following is an example of a string in Javascript?",
        optionA: "[maybeString]",
        optionB: "\"anotherPossibility\"",
        optionC: "aString()",
        optionD: "{stringHere}",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
    // Question 10
    {
        question: "Which symbol is used to seperate Javascript statements?",
        optionA: "Colon ( : )",
        optionB: "Period ( . )",
        optionC: "Semicolon ( ; )",
        optionD: "Modulus ( % )",
        answer: "optionC",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
    // Question 11
    {
        question: "When a user views a page that uses client-side Javascript, what machine is actually executing the script?",
        optionA: "The user's machine running a web browser",
        optionB: "The web server",
        optionC: "One central machine ",
        optionD: "None of the above",
        answer: "optionA",
        isMultChoice: true
    },
        // Question 12
        {
            question: "Which of the following statements is true about Javascript?",
            optionA: "Javascript is an Object-Oriented language",
            optionB: "Javascript is based off Python",
            optionC: "Javascript is an Assembly language",
            optionD: "Javascript is an Object-Based language",
            answer: "optionD",
            isMultChoice: true
        },
 // Question 13
 {
    question: "What is a closure in Javascript?",
    optionA: "When a function is enclosed with references to its inner function scope",
    optionB: "When a function is enclosed with references to its lexical environment",
    optionC: "When a function is enclosed with references to its inner function scope",
    optionD: "When a function is enclosed with references to another file",
    answer: "optionB",
    isMultChoice: true
},
 // Question 14
 {
    question: "Which statement best describes Arrays in Javascript?",
    optionA: "A list of key-value pairs",
    optionB: "An unordered list of values",
    optionC: "An ordered list of values",
    optionD: "None of the above",
    answer: "optionC",
    isMultChoice: true
},
 // Question 15
 {
    question: "The keyword used to refer to an object through which they were invoked is ______?",
    optionA: "from",
    optionB: "this",
    optionC: "object",
    optionD: "outside",
    answer: "optionB",
    isMultChoice: true
},

]